Josephine Schain Papers, 1907-1960
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES V. SUBJECT FILES 1945-57
  - Suffrage
    - Rotogravure sections from The New York Times, 1915 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous pamphlets about peace, 1928-49 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous pamphlets about other subjects, 1908-38, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
- OVERSIZE MATERIALS
  - Articles about Schain in Pictorial Review, Jan & Nov, 1914 (Box 15)
  - Brochures
    - Join the New York Campaign for Peace, 1924 (Box 15)
    - The People's Voice: A Powerful Call to Disarmament, 1932 (Box 15)
    - Fifth Annual Duke Institute of International Relations, Duke University, Jun 1937 (Box 15)
    - Call to the 12th Conference on the Cause and Cure of War, 1937 (Box 15)
    - Peace and Disarmament Committee of the Women's International Organizations, undated (Box 15)
  - Bulletins
    - Women's Club of Minneapolis, Dec 1914 (Box 15)
    - Food and Agriculture Organization, May 1953 (Box 15)
  - Christmas card, undated (Box 15)
  - Delegates' worksheets: 9th-15th Conferences on the Cause and Cure of War, 1934-40 (Box 15)
  - Jupiter Rex Certificate, 1933 (Box 15)
  - Magazine: Illustration de Turque, May 1935 (Box 15)
  - Map: Asia-Minor, published by the Istanbul Hilton, undated (Box 15)
  - Photograph: International Assembly of Women, South Kortright, New York, Oct 1946 (Box 15)
  - Program: Connecticut State Federation of Women's Clubs, undated (Box 15)
  - Brochures (Map-case Flat file)
    - India, undated (Map-case Flat file)
    - Istanbul, Turkey, undated (Map-case Flat file)
  - Maps
    - South Kortright, New York, circa 1946 (hand-drawn, color) (Map-case Flat file)
    - Trust Territories of the Pacific Islands, 1952 (Map-case Flat file)
  - Newsletter: International Labor Organizations, undated (Map-case Flat file)
  - "An Open Letter to President Roosevelt Supporting the Reciprocal Trade Agreement," 1937 (Map-case Flat file)
  - Poll of U.S. Senate on London Naval Pact, 1930 (Map-case Flat file)
  - Posters
    - Announcing speeches by Schain, undated (Map-case Flat file)
    - United Nations: "A Future in the Making," "Rice: Hope for Asia's Millions," and "a Fight for Life," undated (Map-case Flat file)
  - Rotogravure sections from the New York Times, 1915 (Map-case Flat file)